CHARGING THE BATTLE LINES OF THE SIOUX AND THE CHEYENNES!
7th Cavalry is a western film directed by Joseph H. Lewis.
An officer accused of cowardice volunteers to bring back
General Custers's body after Little Big Horn.
Capt. Tom Benson, played by Randolph Scott.
Martha Kellogg, played by Barbara Hale.
Sgt. Bates, played by Jay C. Flippen.
Sgt. Kruger, played by Frank Faylen.
Charlotte Reynolds, played by Jeanette Nolan.
Vogel, played by Leo Gordon.
7th Cavalry is a 1956 American Western film directed by Joseph H.
Lewis and starring Randolph Scott and Barbara Hale.
The script is based on the story "A Horse for Mrs.
Custer" by Glendon Swarthout.
The film is set after the Battle of the Little Bighorn and was filmed in Mexico.
The film explores themes of mission, general, fort.